Can a Boy-Girl Friendship Survive?
(No, It Can't!!)
The Scent of Cherry Sage
So you solve for this double root by...
No way this goes over well.
I'll stay the night, too!
Technically, it's Himari's place, but...
Spending the night with a guy?
Besides, there's that one issue...
What should I bring?
Are you serious about this?
Don't you need your mom's permission?
Does she even know I'll be there?
No prob!
Mom said it's fine since you're a good guy.
Come on, Mom!
Sensei!
This flunky's flirting
with Enocchi during class!
Who said it was Enomoto-san?
Nice try. She just texted me
about staying the night, too.
Really? Is she that excited to sleep over?
We've got a problem.
No studying at my place today!
What? Why not?
I told Onii-chan that Enocchi was coming,
and he went off about not letting
Enomoto DNA step foot on our property.
Hibari-san really hates
Enomoto-san's sister that much?
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Then how about a family restaurant?
If any teachers see us out late,
we'll get written up.
You're right.
You know, Yu.
You get pretty frantic
when it comes to Enocchi.
What are you talking about?
She's only trying to help out.
Hmm.
Really?
You sure you weren't hoping
for a repeat of last night?
Like hell I am!
Natsume!
You've got the nerve to play
around on your smartphone in class?!
After we agreed to let you retake the exams?!
I-I'm sorry.
Bwa-ha!
Hey, there's Natsume-kun!
Hey, so we were talking with Himari-san.
Huh? What?
It's about this account!
Hang on, do you not remember us?
We were in the same class last year.
This!
"You" is actually Natsume-kun, right?
Oh yeah, Himari said something about a leak.
Um, well, even if it were actually me—
Which means?
It's totally true!
I knew Himari-san was hiding something!
Can I help you with something?
Can you make us accessories, too?
We have a friend who really wants one!
U-Umm, well, I'm kinda busy
studying for a retake...
You're retaking the exams?
You seem so smart, though!
Natsu!
What are you doing with these commoners?
Hey, Makishima.
Shoo! He's mine. Go on, now.
Get real!
See ya, Natsume-kun!
See ya.
Let's go before his womanizer
virus rubs off on us!
For sure!
Um, what's up?
I just wanted to ask what I should bring
for the sleepover tonight.
Oh right, that...
I thought she was never
speaking to me again.
But she seems back to normal.
Maybe she forgot with
the whole sleepover thing?
U-Um, actually, I've been
meaning to tell you...
We can't study at my place today.
Oh, okay...
You've sure made a name for yourself, Natsu.
Himari told me you're the reason
for the leak to begin with.
I sure am.
You could at least feel guilty about it.
Never mind that.
Could you help convince Enomoto-san for me?
Convince her? Of what?
So she's spending the night with
her crush under the pretext of studying.
Pretty bold of Rin-chan.
I must say, I'm proud as her
childhood friend and romance advisor.
We're not spending the night,
it's a study group.
Himari will be there, too.
Wait, so you didn't tell her to do that?
It's the first I've heard of it.
I did tell her to be assertive
since you're easily pressured.
You idiot!
Is that a problem?
The girl you love
and the girl who loves you.
A thrilling sleepover
caught between the two.
I've never experienced that,
even when I had five girlfriends.
Natsu, you must be the star of a rom-com.
Stop jabbering and help me out here.
Not my problem.
Do whatever you want.
These are the consequences for your actions.
I know you were getting handsy with
Himari-chan in
the science room the other day.
H-How do you know that?
Don't make me tell you.
You should have at least locked the doors.
Wh-Who was watching? Enomoto-san?
Anyways...
Have fun screwing this up!
So no help from Makishima.
How am I gonna convince Enomoto-san now?
Yu!
About the study group tonight.
We can have it at your place, right?
What?
Well we can't have it at my place.
And anywhere public's a no-go.
So it's gotta be your place!
No way.
You're one thing, but there's no way
I can let Enomoto-san stay the night.
I mean—neither of you can stay!
Come on, you can make up
an excuse about the sleepover.
I'll be there, too.
I dunno...
Enocchi's really excited for it, you know?
And I accidentally told her
we'd do it at your place.
Please!
I felt so bad my place got nixed
at the last minute.
So... Please?
Dammit... She's... too cute!
Himari-san!
'Sup?
We've got Student Council
after school today.
Okay!
What?
Wait, Himari!
Sorry, Yu.
I totally forgot about Student Council.
You two get started without me!
Don't worry! I'll get it over
with in no time!
You've gotta be kidding...
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Why is it like this today of all days?
First thing's first! Gotta start cleaning!
There. That should do it.
Now I just have to make sure
Saku-nee-san doesn't see Enomoto-san.
Come on in!
Hello.
W-Welcome.
Come on inside.
Thanks for having me.
Her outfit's so cute.
And she wore my hair pin.
No one's here, so make yourself at home.
Really?
They're all at the store across the street.
My family owns it.
I work there sometimes, too.
Th-Then it's just us
until Hii-chan comes over?
Something the matter?
Nothing, just...
There's no flowers.
Oh, right.
I store them here so Daifuku
doesn't get into them.
Some flowers are toxic to cats.
Wow, Yu-kun. It's like a world for fairies.
What's this called?
That's cherry sage.
They're known as herbs,
but the flowers have a relaxing scent.
So I like to keep them out
when I'm studying or playing games.
Wow. So you made it both
beautiful and practical.
S-Sure, not that I came up with it.
All right then. Let me start
with a review of yesterday.
Enomoto-san, can you
help me if I get stuck?
Totally. I think I can go over most topics.
I'm actually second in our class.
Perfect scores in four of five subjects.
For real? I didn't expect that.
You didn't?
N-Not like that!
I just had no idea you
were that good at studying.
If you're in second place, then who's first?
They must have had perfect
scores in every subject.
First place is Shii-kun.
Of course he is...
I'll beat him in the finals!
I'm the only one who can't study.
Enomoto-san, can you teach me this part?
Where?
Umm, oh yeah.
You can solve this
by substituting this for x.
Wait, maybe that's not it.
Don't look!
A-Are you thirsty?
I'll get us something to drink.
My heart almost stopped.
Unlike Himari, Enomoto-san
does that unknowingly.
Himari better hurry up
while I can still keep my cool.
Not that I can keep my cool
with her, either.
Upsy-daisy.
Enomoto-san...
I couldn't help it! It was
the scent of cherry sage!
Cherry sage?
It smelled so nice, and then I realized...
The same scent was coming
from your bed, so...
Oh, that.
It's probably this.
I was drinking this on my bed,
and spilled a bit of it.
It's cherry sage tea. Try some.
It smells so good.
That's really good!
You're right.
It smells like cherry sage tea.
That's a bit embarrassing.
Well... I like you, Yu-kun.
Back when Himari and I weren't talking,
Enomoto-san confessed to me
for the first time.
I was preparing to use up all my flowers
so I could go to Tokyo with Himari.
It's not even like I asked for her help.
But before I knew it,
she was making them with me.
I like you.
I've liked you for seven years.
If I hadn't realized my feelings
for Himari back then,
what would I have done?
Since then, Enomoto-san
has been more direct with me.
Phew, done.
Now to check my answers.
She's being super trusting.
Like the day after I turned her down.
She came up to me and said hi like usual.
Better wake her up before Himari gets here.
Enomoto-san, wake up. It's already evening.
W-W-Wait!
How is she still asleep?!
She's like a real-life
character out of a rom-com manga!
Yu! I've arrived...
H-Himari!
It's not what it looks like!
You idiot...
How dare you sneak a girl into the house?
All while having a girl like Himari-chan?
I swear it's not!
We were studying,
but Enomoto-san fell asleep!
Enomoto-san, you're so strong!
How's this possible?
Wake up! I can't move!
It's not funny!
I'm so sorry!
Just thinking of Yu-kun sleeping here
every night made me drift off to sleep...
So you're Kureha's little sister, huh?
Saku-nee-san, you know Enomoto-san's sister?
Know her? We were high school classmates.
We get together with Hibari-kun sometimes
when she's back from Tokyo.
We met this New Year's, too.
With Onii-chan?
Yup. You didn't hear?
Enocchi's sister is
a taboo topic in our house.
That's no surprise from Hibari-kun.
He doesn't like to reveal his weaknesses.
But still...
I'm surprised they don't fight.
Well they're adults, unlike you guys.
My sister can be a bit odd.
So I didn't know she had friends back home.
Thank you for taking care of her.
So, Rion-chan was it?
You don't actually like my idiot brother—
Seriously?
You're so cute, but you
have awful taste in guys.
Just like Kureha.
Sorry about Saku-nee-san.
I think she's a great older sister.
You do?
She's better than my sister,
who came back during New Year's
but couldn't be bothered
to give any of us family members a heads up.
Okay...
But you know...
Just something I noticed.
Neither of you seemed too
bothered by Sakura-san teasing you.
Enomoto-san confessed
to me during our fight.
Wh-What?!
And you still tried to go to Tokyo with me?
What's wrong with you?
Well, I turned her down.
B-But you've both been so normal.
Isn't that usually an awkward situation?
She's actually confessed
three times already.
Three times?
If I count that last one, four times.
J-Just now? All while I was gone?
Yes, I did.
Yu, what the heck?!
Taking advantage of Enocchi
and keeping her around?
That's not like you!
Um, well I turn her down every time.
But it's always business as usual
the next day, and she bakes me cookies.
Don't get lured in by cookies!
H-Hey Himari, calm down.
You can't be wishy washy like that!
Even if she is your first crush!
First crush?
Yu-kun, is that true?
Himari!
Why are you exposing me like that?
I'm sorry!
You're my first crush, but I'm not sure
if that means I like you now.
And I can't accept your offer
just because you're pretty.
Yu-kun...
Gotcha! Good to know for next time!
What was that memo?
Man, you're optimistic.
Anyways, what about you two?
You seemed awkward until this morning.
Oh yeah! Hmph!
That's not very convincing.
I totally forgot.
I wasn't supposed to talk to Hii-chan.
You weren't?
From a couple days ago.
She messaged me.
That didn't last long.
Enomoto-san, you forgot after
the whole study group thing, didn't you?
Because Hii-chan said she supported me.
Then she went and tried
to take you to Tokyo.
I guess that's partly my fault, too.
But I know that I don't deserve
to get mad over that.
Shii-kun told me that I shouldn't complain
until I've worked hard to be number one.
Hii-chan's worked two years
to be Yu-kun's number one.
I haven't worked at all in seven years.
I have no right to criticize Hii-chan.
That's why I'll become both Yu-kun
and Hii-chan's number one!
Come again?
If I become Yu-kun's number one
and Hii-chan's number one friend,
everything works out, right?
So she would feel bad
coming between Himari and me,
so instead, she's gonna
take both of us for herself?
Is this a threat? What kind of
wartime general is she?
Uh, Enomoto-san...
After thinking about it, Hii-chan's
worked really hard as the main model.
So I should respect that role as hers.
U-Um, thanks.
Besides, if I'm gonna work hard for Yu-kun,
I can't just copy her.
That's why I was hoping
to help you behind the scenes.
What do you think?
If you're okay with that.
Yay! That works better for me anyways
since I have club after school.
If I learn more about
online orders and shipping,
I bet I can help out more
with my family's cake shop, too!
Well if that's the case, great.
Enocchi's stubborn when she gets like this.
I think it's a great idea.
Then we'd love to work with you!
Great! I'll do my best!
Let's celebrate the new You team!
You do realize what you just did, right?
Letting Enomoto's little sister join you.
It couldn't be helped.
She was so sincere about us being friends.
Honestly, I know I did
a terrible thing by telling her
I'd support her then going behind her back.
Onii-chan, I heard you still
hang out with Kureha-san.
Sakura-kun told you?
She always lets things slip.
You're still not over her?
Never mind me, worry about yourself.
Why?
Not only did you mistake the balance
between friendship and romance,
you chose the wrong partner
to create accessories with.
First, your emotions got the best of you,
and Yu-kun had to retake his exams.
Now, you're holding Yu-kun back under
the guise of being his best friend.
If you can't help each other be better,
you have no right to stand beside him.
It's not like Yu-kun's dream
depends on your support.
I could just adopt him
into the Inuzuka family.
Onii-chan, you never think
about anyone besides Yu.
So? What am I supposed to do now?
Stop lying to Yu-kun.
Lying?
You have a habit of preparing
an escape route.
Until you fix that, you'll lose to Enomoto's
sister and never be Yu-kun's equal.
I understand. I accept that challenge.
Very well then.
How about some treats on the way home?
Really?
It's my fault for not being able to
let Enomoto's sister in our house.
Buy whatever you'd like.
Thanks, Onii-chan!
Then I want some ice cream
or black Mont Blanc!
Oh yeah, Onii-chan.
About the no lying thing,
what's considered a lie?
Himari! That's the problem with you!
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to!
It was a reflex!
That kind of thoughtless banter
risks Yu-kun losing his cool!
I understand!
I'll be an honest person
so I can be Yu's equal!
Exam Retake Day
See?
If you can get a perfect score,
do the work to begin with!
Sorry about that!
Thankfully, I got
by without having to quit high school.
The Cracked Crocus